&GT；&GT；凯尔·辛普森：七年前，马克给了我教书的开始。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Seven years ago, Mark gave me my start in teaching.
他联系了我，看到我在做会议演讲，但是
He reached out to me, had seen me giving conference talks, but
我从来没有教过这个行业的任何东西。
I had never taught anything in this industry, whatsoever.
他伸手说，嘿，我想你应该试一试。
And he reached out and said, hey, I think you should give it a shot.
他花了几周时间哄我，
And he took a couple of weeks to coax me,
主要是因为我要去明尼苏达州冰天雪地。
mostly because I was having to come up to snowy, cold Minnesota.
但他花了几个星期的时间哄我，我来到这里，给我的第一个研讨会。
But he took a couple weeks to coax me and I came up here and gave my first workshop.
那天过半的时候，我突然想到这就是我想要做的，
And midway through that day, it clicked in my mind that this is what I wanted to do,
这就是我在这里的目的，就是教书。
and this is what I'm here for, is to teach.
所以我现在是一名全职教师，这完全多亏了马克。
So I'm a teacher now full-time, thanks completely to Mark.
所以我一直很感激这一点，我总是觉得我要回家了，
So I always appreciate that and I always feel like I'm coming back home,
如果你愿意，当我回到前端大师的时候。
if you will, when I come back to Frontend Masters.
因此，本课程，我们将讨论JavaScript和
So this course, we're gonna be talking about JavaScript and
我们会比你习惯的更深入地讨论这件事。
we're gonna be talking about it much more deeply than you're used to likely going.
大多数人可能知道我有一个公平的
Most people may know that I have a fairly
名为GETIFY的强大在线存在。
strong online presence under the name GETIFY.
所以如果你读过我的推特流，特别是最近，
So if you've read my Twitter streams, especially lately,
在准备课程的时候，我已经谈论了很多关于这些的东西。
I've been talking a lot about all this stuff while preparing the course.
但你可以在我的推特上，在GitHub上找到我所有的想法
But you can find all of my thoughts on my Twitter, on GitHub,
这是我的电子邮件地址。
that's my email address.
所以，请随时联系或寻找更多的信息。
So feel free to reach out or look for more of that information.
我已经写了很多书，包括“你不知道JS”系列书。
I've written a number of books including the You Don't Know JS book series.
本课程中的许多材料都直接与前三本主要书籍有关
A lot of material from this course tracks directly with the first three major books
系列中的。
of the series.
范围和闭包一书，这&amp；对象原型一书，以及
The Scope and Closures book, the This &amp; Object Prototypes book, and
类型和语法书。
the Types &amp; Grammar book.
因此，这些是本课程结束后获取更多信息的最佳去处。
So those are the best places to go after this course to get more information.
你可以免费阅读，也可以购买。
You can read those for free or you can purchase them.
如果你喜欢的话，我总是很感激你的购买。
I always appreciate purchases if you like those.
所以我想和你谈谈为什么我们要跳到JavaScript
So I wanna talk to you a little bit about why we're gonna jump into JavaScript so
更深。
much more deeply.
与其对每一种可能的框架和缩略语进行广泛的调查，
Rather than a broad survey of every kind of framework and acronym that's possible,
为什么我们要深入研究JavaScript，为什么这在今天还很重要？
why are we diving deep into JavaScript, and why does that even matter today?
因为似乎趋势是没有人再写JavaScript了。
Because it seems the trend is nobody even writes JavaScript anymore.
他们写别的东西，不管是打字稿还是
They write something else, whether it's TypeScript or
一种完全不同的语言，比如GO或Closure。
an entirely different language like Go or Closure.
但似乎没有人真正编写自己的JavaScript。
But nobody seems to really write their JavaScript.
我的意思是，甚至没有人再发布他们写的JavaScript了。
I mean, nobody even ships JavaScript that they wrote anymore.
它们提供了14层Babble转换所完成的代码。
They ship the code that 14 layers of Babble transformations have done.
那么为什么我们学习和理解
So why does it even matter why we learn and understand and
为什么我们应该学习和理解JavaScript？
why should we learn and understand JavaScript?
所以我想，只是简短的介绍一下，这是我们将要报道的内容的概述。
So I wanna, just a quick brief, this is an overview of what we're gonna be covering.
这显然是非常简单的代码，但是
This is obviously very simple code, but
这实际上是我经历过的或者
this is actually something that I experienced or
我最近才了解到，在这门课程的准备和准备中。
I learned just recently, in the preparation and buildup to this course.
所以你们中的大多数人可能知道+运算符。
So most of you probably know about the ++ operator.
当它出现在后缀位置时，就像第3行上的这里一样，
And that when it shows up in the postfix position, like it is here on line 3,
当它出现在后缀位置时，它是后置增量。
when it shows up in that postfixed position it's an after increment.
所以它给出值，然后递增，这就是为什么x+仍然返回
So it gives you the value and then it increments, which is why x++ still returns
US 40，但x已更新为41。
us 40, but then x has been updated to 41.
然后在第6行，我们有执行更新的预增量
And then on line 6 we have the pre-increment which does the updating
首先，然后返回值，这就是为什么在该行上我们同时得到42。
first and then returns the value, which is why on that line we get both 42s.
现在，我已经在我的头脑中，我认为大多数开发人员已经在他们的头脑中有一个心理
Now I've had in my head and I think most developers have had in their head a mental
+运算符正在执行的操作的模型。
model for what the ++ operator is doing.
是的，有之前和之后的细微差别，但是
Yes, there's the before and after kind of nuance, but
在我的脑海里，这个+运算符基本上就是x+1。
I've had in my mind that essentially, this ++ operator is basically x+1.
我想大多数人可能认为情况就是这样。
And I think most people probably think that that is the case.
所以我特别深入研究了这一点
And so I was digging into this in particular, and
你会在后面的课程中发现我为什么这么想
you'll find out later in the course why I was thinking so
对像这样细微差别的东西深有感触。
deeply about something as sort of nuanced as this.
但我在想，如果你在某个值上有+，它是不是在
But I was trying to think about if you have ++ on some value and it's in
后缀位置，这是否意味着返回的值完全原封不动？
the postfix position, does that mean that the value comes back completely untouched?
我假设情况就是这样，它返回的是完全原封不动的值
I assumed that that was the case, that it returned the value completely untouched
然后它做了它更新的任何增量。
and then it made whatever increments it updated.
所以问题就变成了，当你在后缀中使用+时会发生什么
So the question then becomes, well, what happens when you use ++ in that postfix
位置，但是你在一些还不是数字的值上使用它？
position, but you use it on some value that's not already a number?
我们将在这门课上讲一点关于类型和
And we're gonna be talking in just a little bit in this course about types and
胁迫。
coercion.
我将真正深入这个话题。
And I'm gonna get real deep into this topic.
但问题是，
But the question becomes,
当有一个数字的字符串表示和
what happens when there's a string representation of a number and
然后你做一些基本的数学运算，比如递增？
then you do something fundamentally mathematic like incrementing it?
在我的思维过程中，再一次，因为把x+想成x等于x+1，
In my mind thought process, again, because thinking of x++ as x equals x+1,
我在想，好吧，它会返回这个字符串5，然后
I was thinking, well, it will return this string 5, and
然后它将强制字符串5为数字5，并将其更新为6。
then it'll coerce that string 5 to the number 5 and update it to 6.
这就是我的心智模型。
That was the mental model I had.
事实证明，即使这看起来是合理的，但事实并非如此。
And it turns out that even though that seems reasonable, that's not what happens.
结果是它先进行并强制它到一个数字，或者
It turns out that it goes ahead and coerces it to a number first, or
至少看起来是这样。
at least that's what appears to happen.
你注意到我没有在第7行取回字符串5，
You notice that I didn't get back the string 5 there on line 7,
我拿回了5号
I got back the number 5.
所以在某种意义上，它确实进行了修改，
So it does go ahead and modify, in a sense,
如果需要在进行任何递增之前将其强制为一个数字，则为该值。
the value if it needs to coerce it to a number, before it does any incrementing.
所以它甚至不是一个真正的后遗症，它在某种程度上是在中间。
So it's not even really an after, it's sort of in the middle.
这是一件奇怪的事情。
It's kind of a strange thing.
这是我以前从未想到的细微差别。
And this was a nuance that had never occurred to me before.
现在，我并不是建议您在代码中遇到这些问题。
Now I'm not suggesting that you're gonna run across these problems in code.
但这是为了说明一个更大的问题，
But this is to be illustrative of a larger point,
这就是我们作为开发人员倾向于假设关于代码的心理模型。
which is that we as developers tend to assume mental models about code.
然后当虫子发生时，我说什么时候，而不是如果，
And then when bugs happen, and I say when, not if,
当错误发生时，我们责怪语言，对吗？
when bugs happen we blame the language, right?
我们责怪语言。
We blame the language.
显然，JavaScript的设计一定很糟糕，因为发生了这种情况。
JavaScript clearly must have been designed poorly because this happened.
现在我有很多意见。
Now I have lots of opinions.
那些关注我的人都知道，我对JavaScript有很多看法。
Those that follow me know, I have lots of opinions on JavaScript.
我从来不会对这些东西感到迷茫。
I'm never at a loss for those.
我喜欢说我唯一的专家就是我自己的观点，对吧？
I like to say the only thing I'm an expert on is my own opinions, right?
我从来不会对这些东西感到迷茫。
I'm never at a loss for those.
所以我对某些特定的东西是不是好还是不好有很多看法
So I have lots of opinions on whether or not some particular thing was a good or
在JavaScript设计中做出明智或明智的决定。
smart or wise decision in the design of JavaScript.
但我从不认为合适的是
But what I never think is appropriate is for
我们去拿一些我们感到惊讶的东西
us to take something where we get surprised and
说，因为我们很惊讶，所以JavaScript是错误的。
say, because we're surprised, therefore JavaScript is at fault.
如果你问一屋子的C+开发人员，
If you ask a room of C++ developers,
你读过C+规范的任何部分吗？
have you ever read any part of the specification for C++?
大多数人都会举手，Java也是如此。
Most hands will go up, same for Java.
但是如果我问同样的问题，而且我确实这么做了，全世界我都会问这个问题
But if I ask that same question, and I do, all over the world I ask this question
几乎每次都有多少人读过JavaScript规范的任何部分？
almost every time, how many of you have read any part of the JavaScript spec?
而且我几乎没有得到任何人的手。
And I hardly ever get any hands.
我认为我在这里得到的部分是许多开发人员
And I think part of what I'm getting at here is that many developers in
JavaScript社区似乎认为JavaScript对
the JavaScript community seem to think that JavaScript with its low barrier to
进入，应该是如此自动地可理解，如此直观，
entry, should be so automatically understandable, so intuitive,
如果它不是立即直观的，因此它设计得很差。
that if it's not immediately intuitive, therefore it was poorly designed.
好像我们没有责任去学习我们的工具是如何工作的。
As if we don't own a responsibility to learn how our tool works.
所以如果你在寻找我教的东西的总体主题
So if you're looking for any sort of overarching theme to what I teach and
为什么我教，特别是这门课，那还不够好
why I teach and specifically this course, it is that that's not good enough
作为开发人员，我们要假设一些事情，我们的假设是不正确的。
as developers for us to assume something, our assumption to be incorrect.
然后当我们被它咬伤时，我们就把责任转移到别人身上。
And then when we get bitten by it we shift the blame to someone else.
而不是其他社区的大多数开发人员说，
Instead of most developers in other communities saying,
好吧，这是我自己的错。
well, the fault is my own.
我还不够明白，好吗？
I didn't understand it enough, okay?
所以在这里，当我体验到作为数字5而不是字符串5回来时，
So here, when I experienced it coming back as the number 5 instead of the string 5,
我没说，愚蠢的JavaScript，你怎么会设计得这么差？
I didn't say, stupid JavaScript, how could you be so poorly designed?
我的问题是为什么，具体是什么？
My question was why, what specifically?
只有一个方法可以回答这个问题。
And there's really only one way to answer that question.
所以问题是你有没有读过说明书的任何部分
So the question of have you ever read any part of the specification
真的是一个永远存在的问题，你应该经常问自己。
is really an ever-present question that you should always be asking yourself.
如果我不明白某件事，权力的来源在哪里？
If I don't understand something, where is that source of authority?
我最近真的有过这样的争论，有人说，我不知道，
I actually had this argument recently where somebody said, I don't know,
JavaScript引擎是权威的来源。
the JavaScript engine is the source of authority.
不，不是。
No, it isn't.
规范是权威的来源。
The specification is the source of authority.
如果你想知道为什么某些东西会这样做，为什么我会看到这种行为？
And if you're wondering why does something do it, why am I seeing this behavior?
为什么它看起来怪异或神秘或黑匣子或马车或其他什么？
Why does it seem weird or mysterious or black box or buggy or whatever?
您需要问的第一个问题是规范说应该发生什么？
The first question you need to ask is what does the specification say should happen?
然后问我现在看到的我的行为是否符合规格？
And then ask does my behavior that I'm seeing match the spec?
如果它们不匹配，好吧，那你就有问题了。
If they don't match, well, then you have a bug.
但是如果它们真的匹配，那么你就会有一种不同类型的bug
But if they do match, then you have a different sort of a bug and
这是你大脑里的一个错误的想法。
it's a bug inside of your brain which is incorrect thinking.